YUSRIL

Bumi Batara Mawang AA3/08, Gowa, South Sulawesi **Mob:** 0852 4221 9608 **Email:** yusril09@outlook.com

SUMMARY

I am a fourth year Informatics Engineering student at Hasanuddin University. I was responsible for Web Development specialize on back-end development which is related to solving the problem in terms of business logic to deliver the best system functionality. I have experience working with PHP Laravel and also make Rest- API. I also have an interest in mobile development by taking part in the Bangkit program 2021. And then last but not least i also have a good communication and love to work as a team.

EXPERIENCE

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka - Participant

Feb 2021 - present

Learning mobile application module path in Dicoding from basic until expert.

PT. PLN (Persero) UIW Sulselrabar - Developer Intern

Oct 2020 - Nov 2020

I've experienced to developed cms administrator and rest-API using PHP Laravel for the KNCH PLN mobile application.

Part Time Web Developer

Des 2020 - Feb 2021

I build responsive website with Bootstrap and use Laravel Framework as Back-End to provide Rest-API. I made an automatic letter printing application from the database into a pdf file that can be accessed by every employee.

Indonesia Android Kejar - Partisipant

Des 2017

Learning basic mobile application from professional mentor.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering (GPA 3.38)

Hasanuddin University 2017 - Now

SKILLS

- Laravel (PHP Framework)
 Intermediate
- Javascript Basic
- GIT Basic

- Bootstrap (CSS framework) Intermediate
- Kotlin Intermediate
- MySQL Basic